http://www.ensco.com/legal#caprivacy

Skip to main content
ENSCO Legal Information
Website Terms and Conditions
By visiting this site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree with the following.
Privacy Policy
Effective date: 1/1/2020
ENSCO, Inc. owns and operates this website (www.ensco.com) (“Site”). This Privacy Policy tells you how we collect, use and share information we collect on the Site effective as of the date posted above. By using the Site and submitting information you agree that we may use and disclose your information according to the terms of this Policy.
Information collected and how it is used
We automatically collect information when you visit the Site including your device’s IP address, and statistics about how you use the Site.
We collect information that you submit when visiting the site including contact information if you contact us with an inquiry (email address, telephone number), register for an event, or information you choose to submit when exploring a career opportunity with ENSCO. Our Careers page is powered by a third party service provider who receives the information that you submit and who transfers that information to us.
We use the collected information for our general commercial purposes such as to improve our Site, grow our business and to offer our own, our affiliates’ or third-party products or services that we think you may find of interest. We use your contact information to respond to your inquiries or to provide information on products or services to you.
We use cookies and similar technology to collect aggregate (non-personal) information about Site usage by all of our visitors and to help us remember you and your preferences when you revisit the Site. These cookies may stay on your browser into the future until they expire, or you delete them. These cookies usually are erased when you close your browser window. Further general information about cookies and how they work is available at www.allaboutcookies.org.
We may allow selected third parties to place cookies through the Site to provide us with better insights into the use of the Site or user demographics or to provide relevant advertising to you. These third parties may collect information about a consumer’s online activities over time and across different websites when he or she uses our website. We may also permit third party service providers to place cookies through our Site to perform analytic or marketing functions where you are notified of them and you have consented to the usage. We do not control the use of such third-party cookies or the resulting information and we are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.
We do use technology that recognizes a “do-not-track” signal from your web browser. This technology allows us to exclude you from any analytics that collect information about your online activities over time and across third party websites.
Children’s Privacy
This Site is not designed nor intended to be attractive to use by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 please do not submit any information to us.
Accessing your information and your choices
You can choose not to receive emails from us by “unsubscribing” using the instructions in any email you receive from us. This will not stop us from sending emails about your transactions with us.
You can choose to delete or block cookies by setting your browser to either reject all cookies or to allow cookies only from selected sites. If you block cookies performance of the Site may be impaired and certain features may not function at all.
Sharing your information
We may reveal information about you to unaffiliated third parties: (1) if you request or authorize it; (2) if the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you; (3) if the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); (4) if the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); (5) if the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, processing orders, etc.); or (6) as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.
We may share your information with our affiliated companies, and they are permitted to use it for their commercial purposes including marketing.
We do not share your information with third parties for their marketing purposes.
We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-Personal Information, such as usage statistics, to our affiliates and third parties.
Your California Privacy Rights
California residents are permitted by California law to request information about the manner in which we share certain categories of information with others for their marketing purposes.
We do not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing use unless we have your permission. To withdraw permission previously granted please email us at info@ensco.com. Once we receive your instruction, we will cease sharing your information, but this will not affect previously shared information.
Security
We use reasonable technical, administrative and physical measures to protect information contained in our system against misuse, loss or alteration. We may use standard SSL technology to protect information being transferred to our site, but no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure. If we receive instructions using your log-in information we will consider that you have authorized the instructions.
Data Processing and Cross-Border Data Transfers
Our Site is maintained on servers located in the United States, and personal information submitted is stored on our servers in the United States. If you are visiting our Site from outside the United States, please be advised that your information is transferred to our U.S. servers. Disclosing your personal information to us pursuant to this Privacy Policy is at your own risk. We strive to comply with laws of jurisdictions in which we maintain operations but we make no representations that the practices described in this Privacy Policy are compliant with laws outside those jurisdictions that apply to the collection, security, use and disclosure of personal information.
For site visitors from Nevada
We do not transfer personal information for monetary consideration. If you would like to tell us not to sell your information in the future please email us at info@ensco.com or writing to us at 5400 Port Royal Road, Springfield, Virginia 22151 with your name, postal address, telephone number and email address with “Nevada do not sell” in the subject line.
For California Residents: Consumer Privacy Act Rights
As of January 1, 2020, verified California residents will have the right to:
request and receive disclosure of our personal information collection practices during the prior 12 months, including the categories of personal information we collect, the categories of sources of such information, our business purpose for collecting or sharing such information, and the categories of third parties with whom we share such information.
request and receive a copy of the personal information we have collected about them during the prior 12 months.
request and receive disclosure of our information sale practices during the prior 12 months, including a list of the categories of personal information sold and the category of third party recipients and a list of the categories of personal information that we disclosed for a business purpose.
request that we not sell personal information about them and
request that we delete (and direct our service providers to delete) their personal information subject to certain exceptions.
In order to make a request for disclosure California residents may contact us by info@ensco.com or by calling us toll-free at +1-800-ENSCO-VA.
We will ask you for information that allows us to reasonably verify your identity (that you are the person about whom we collected personal information) and will use that information only for that purpose. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity and confirm that the personal information relates to you.
You may make a request up to twice within a 12-month period. We will endeavor to respond within forty-five days of receipt of your request, but if we require more time (up to an additional forty-five days) we will notify you of our need for additional time.
For requests for a copy of the personal information we have collected during the 12 months prior to your request we will endeavor to provide the information in a format that is readily useable, including by mailing you a paper copy or providing an electronic copy to your registered account, if you have registered an account with us.
We will not discriminate against you as a result of your exercise of any of these rights.
During the past 12 months, we have collected the following categories of information from the listed sources, used it for the listed business purposes and shared it with the listed categories of third parties. The categories of information include information we collect from our website visitors, registered users, employees, vendors, suppliers and any other person that interacts with us either online or offline. Not all information is collected about all individuals. For instance, we may collect different information from applicants for employment or from vendors or from customers.
Category of Information collected
Source
**describe source or state Not Collected
Business purposes* for use
**describe appropriate purpose or Not Collected
Categories of third parties receiving information
**select appropriate category or state Not Shared
Identifiers
(name, alias, postal address, email address, phone number, fax number, account name, Social Security number, driver's license number, passport number, unique personal identifier, IP address)
Individuals submitting information to us;
information we automatically collect from site visitors;
information we may receive from third-party marketing and data partners.
Auditing relating to transactions;
security detection, protection and enforcement;
functionality debugging/error repair;
ad customization;
performing services for you;
internal research and development;
quality control.
Service providers (such as payment processors, mail houses, marketing partners, shipping partners, employee benefits partners);
affiliated companies;
government regulators;
law enforcement;
strategically aligned businesses;
Sensitive Information
(name with financial account, medical, health, and health insurance information, username and password)
Individuals submitting information;
employment applications;
employees.
Auditing relating to transactions;
security detection, protection and enforcement;
functionality debugging/error repair; ad customization;
performing services for you;
internal research and development;
quality control.
Service providers (such as payment processors, employee benefits partners),
Protected classification information
(race, gender, ethnicity, religion)
Individuals submitting information.
Auditing relating to transactions;
security detection, protection and enforcement;
functionality debugging/error repair;
ad customization;
performing services for you;
internal research and development;
quality control.
Service providers (such as employee benefits partners).
Commercial information
(transaction history, products/services purchased, obtained or considered, product preference)
Individuals submitting information;
information we automatically collect from site visitors;
information we may receive from third-party marketing or data partners.
Auditing relating to transactions;
security detection, protection and enforcement;
functionality debugging/error repair;
ad customization;
performing services to you;
internal research and development;
quality control.
Service providers (such as payment processors, mail houses, marketing partners, shipping partners, employee benefits partners),
affiliated companies,
government regulators,
law enforcement,
strategically aligned businesses,
Electronic network activity
(browsing or search history, website interactions, advertisement interactions)
Information automatically collected from site visitors.
Auditing relating to transactions;
security detection, protection and enforcement;
functionality debugging/error repair;
ad customization;
performing services for you;
internal research and development;
quality control.
Service providers (such as payment processors, mail houses, marketing partners, shipping partners, employee benefits partners);
affiliated companies;
government regulators;
law enforcement;
strategically aligned businesses.
Audio, video or similar information
(customer service calls, security monitoring)
Individuals submitting information;
information we collect for security purposes.
Auditing relating to transactions;
security detection, protection and enforcement;
functionality debugging/error repair;
ad customization;
performing services for you;
internal research and development;
quality control.
Service providers (such as payment processors, mail houses, marketing partners, shipping partners, employee benefits partners);
affiliated companies;
government regulators;
law enforcement;
strategically aligned businesses.
Biometrics
Individuals submitting information
Information we collect for security purposes
Auditing relating to transactions;
security detection, protection and enforcement;
functionality debugging/error repair;
ad customization;
performing services for you;
internal research and development;
quality control.
Service providers (such as payment processors, mail houses, marketing partners, shipping partners, employee benefits partners);
affiliated companies;
government regulators;
law enforcement;
strategically aligned businesses.
Geolocation
Information we automatically collect from site visitors.
Auditing relating to transactions;
security detection, protection and enforcement;
functionality debugging/error repair;
ad customization;
performing services for you;
internal research and development;
quality control.
Service providers (such as payment processors, mail houses, marketing partners, shipping partners, employee benefits partners);
affiliated companies;
government regulators;
law enforcement;
strategically aligned businesses.
Professional, educational or employment related information
Information submitted by individuals;
information received from third parties in connection with vendor or employment status or applications;
information we observe in connection with vendor or employment oversight.
Auditing relating to transactions;
security detection, protection and enforcement;
functionality debugging/error repair;
ad customization;
performing services for you;
internal research and development;
quality control.
Service providers (such as payment processors, employee benefits partners);
government regulators;
law enforcement.
Inference from the above
(preferences, characteristics, behavior, attitudes, abilities, etc.)
Internal analytics
Auditing relating to transactions;
security detection, protection and enforcement;
functionality debugging/error repair;
ad customization;
performing services for you;
internal research and development;
quality control.
*More specifically, the business purposes include:
Performing services for you:
To administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement to which we are a party;
To assist you in completing a transaction or order;
To allow tracking of shipments;
To prepare and process invoices;
To respond to queries or requests and to provide services and support;
To provide aftersales customer relationship management;
To create and manage our customer accounts;
To notify you about changes to our services and products;
To administer any promotion, contest, survey, or competition;
To provide you information regarding our products and services,
To offer our products and services to you in a personalized way, for example, we may provide suggestions based on your previous requests to enable you to identify suitable products and services more quickly.
Advertising customization.
For marketing and promotions, we believe you may find of interest and to provide you, or allow selected third parties to provide you, with information about products and services that may interest you;
Auditing relating to transactions, internal research and development.
To provide for internal business administration and operations, including troubleshooting, Site customization, enhancement or development, testing, research, administration and operation of our Sites and data analytics;
To create products or services that may meet your needs;
To measure performance of marketing initiatives, ads, and websites “powered by” another company on our behalf;
Security detection, protection and enforcement; functionality debugging, error repair.
As part of our efforts to keep our Sites safe and secure;
To ensure the security of your account and our business, preventing or detecting fraud, malicious activity or abuses of our Sites, for example, by requesting verification information in order to reset your account password (if applicable);
To ensure the physical security of our premises through the monitoring of surveillance images;
To resolve disputes, to protect the rights, safety and interests ourselves, our users or others, and to comply with our legal obligations.
Quality control.
To monitor quality control and ensure compliance with our legal obligations, codes and ordinances, policies and procedures,
To develop and improve our products and services, for example, by reviewing visits to the Sites and various subpages, demand for specific products and services and user comments;
Links to other sites
We may permit others to link to this Site or to post a link to their site on ours. We do not endorse these sites and are not responsible for other sites or their privacy practices. Please read their privacy policies before submitting information.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
As we grow and change, we may amend this Privacy Policy. The Policy in effect at the time you use the Site governs how we may use your information. If we make material changes, we will post the revised Policy and the revised effective date on this Site. Please check back here from time to time to review any changes.
Contacting us
This Site is owned and operated by ENSCO. You can contact us via email at info@ensco.com or writing to us at 5400 Port Royal Road, Springfield, Virginia 22151 or by calling us toll-free at +1-800-ENSCO-VA.
Export Controls
The export of certain information, data, software and documentation may, due to its nature or intended use or final destination, be subject to U.S. Export Control Laws, including the U.S. Department of Commerce Export Administration Regulations and/or the U.S. Department of State International Traffic in Arms Regulations. By downloading or using any information, data, software or documentation from this server, you are agreeing to comply strictly with all such applicable laws.
Use of Content
The content found on www.ensco.com is the property of ENSCO, Inc. and its wholly owned U.S. subsidiaries. This includes text, graphics, logos, images, photos and videos. This content may not be used without the prior written permission of ENSCO.
Trademarks
Names, trademarks, servicemarks, and logos that appear on this site may not be used in advertising or promotion without prior written permission from ENSCO, Inc.
Copyrights
All content on this site is protected by U.S. copyright law, and as such may not be copied or duplicated in any way without express written permission from ENSCO, Inc.
Disclaimer
Inclusion of third party links does not imply endorsement or recommendation by ENSCO, Inc. In addition, ENSCO makes no warranties as to the accuracy of information contained in these sites.
On occasion, ENSCO, Inc. will update these terms and conditions.
Print
